htcampus.com 2018-07-23

# Privacy Policy HTCampus

The Privacy Policy provided below is with respect to our use and protection of any personal information you provide to us through the www.htcampus.com website. Firefly e-Ventures Limited (hereinafter referred to as FEVL) is the sole owner of the website www.htcampus.com . The Policy is applicable to the website. It may also be applicable generally to our other related websites provided it appears at the footer of the page therein. You may be required to provide personally identifiable information at several different points on our website. By accepting the policy at the time of registration, you expressly approve and consent to our collection, storage, use and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Policy.

**Use of Website**

If you choose to provide us with the abovementioned information, you consent to the use, transfer and storage of the information so provided by you on our servers. The information provided by you shall be used by us, including but not limited, to:

  * Improve our website and enable us to provide you the most user-friendly experience which is safe, smooth and customized;
  * Improve and customize our services, content and other commercial /non - commercial features on the website;
  * Send you information through Any Medium including (not limited to) SMS, e-mail, other communication material, etc Services for education information in respect of our products, services, special deals, promotions etc;
  * Send you marketing/promotional communications.
  * Send newsletter(s) to you (Provided you subscribe to the same);
  * Send you service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so;
  * Provide you the opportunity to participate in contests or surveys on our website (If you participate, we may request certain additional personally identifiable information from you. Moreover, participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you therefore shall have a choice whether or not to disclose such additional information);
  * Provide customer support and the services you request;
  * Resolve disputes, if any and troubleshooting;
  * Avoid/check illegal and/or potentially prohibited activities and to enforce Agreements ;
  * Provide service updates and promotional offers related to our services/products.
  * Comply with any court judgment / decree / order / directive / legal & government authority /applicable law;
  * Investigate potential violations or applicable national & international laws;
  * Investigate deliberate damage to the website/services or its legitimate operation;
  * Detect, prevent, or otherwise address security and/or technical issues;
  * Protect the rights, property or safety of FEVL and/or its Directors, employees and the general public at large; and
  * Respond to Claims of third parties;
  * To carry out our own analysis and research.

If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our website, we will ask you for your friend's name and email address. We will automatically send your friend an email inviting him or her to visit the website. However, your friend may contact us to request that he does not require such services/content/email or we remove the information related to him from our database. Based upon the personally identifiable information you provide us, we will send you a welcoming email to verify your username and password. We will also communicate with you in response to your inquiries with respect to our services/content, to provide the services you request, and to manage your account. We will communicate with you by email and / or telephone, in accordance with your wishes. In order to provide certain services to you, we may on occasion supplement the personal information you submitted to us with information from third party sources (third parties for this purpose may include our group / holding / subsidiary companies and or our service partners / associates). We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our website.

**Information Collection**

When you visit/surf our website, certain personal information including but not limited to your name, email address, contact address, mobile/telephone number(s), sex, age, occupation, interests, credit card information, billing information, financial information, content, IP address, standard web log information, information about your computer hardware and software and such other information as may be required for your interaction for the services and from which your identity is discernible may be automatically stored with us. However, if you choose to avail of certain services on our website, you shall be required to provide certain personal information for the registration and/or access to such services/web pages. Such information may include, without limitation, your name, email address, contact address, mobile/telephone number(s), sex, age, occupation, interests, credit card information, billing information, financial information, content, IP address, standard web log information, information about your computer hardware and software and such other information as may be required for your interaction with the services and from which your identity is discernible. We may also collect demographic information that is not unique to you such as code, preferences, favorites, etc. Further, sometimes you may be asked to provide descriptive, cultural, preferential and social & life style information.

In addition to the above we may indirectly also collect information about you when you use certain third party services available on our website. We may also collect certain information about the use of our website by you, such as the services you access/use or areas you visit.

**Automatically-Collected Information.**

We may automatically collect information about the computer or devices (including mobile devices) you use to access the Services. For example, we may collect and store information such as your browser type, IP address, language, operating system, location of your wireless device (e.g., latitude and longitude), the state or country from which you accessed the Services, the pages you view, the services you use, the date and time of your visit, the websites you visited immediately before and after visiting our websites, error logs, and other hardware and software information. We may use third party analytics providers and technologies, including cookies and similar tools, to assist in collecting this information. We may use this information to formulate statistical models about use of the Services, enhance the Services for our users, and provide you with tailored content and advertising.

We use data collection devices such as "cookies" on certain pages of the Site to help analyze our web page flow, measure promotional effectiveness, and promote trust and safety. "Cookies" are small files placed on your hard drive that assist us in providing our services. We offer certain features that are only available through the use of a "cookie". We also use cookies to allow you to enter your password less frequently during a session. Cookies can also help us provide information that is targeted to your interests. Most cookies are "session cookies," meaning that they are automatically deleted from your hard drive at the end of a session. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, although in that case you may not be able to use certain features on the Site and you may be required to reenter your password more frequently during a session.

Additionally, you may encounter "cookies" or other similar devices on certain pages of the Site that are placed by third parties. For example, if you view a web page created by a user, there may be a "cookie" placed within that web page. We do not control the use of cookies by third parties.

If you choose to bid, buy or sell on the Site, we collect information about your bidding, buying and selling behavior. We also collect other users' comments about you in our feedback area.

**User-Initiated Communication.**

From time to time, portions of the Services may enable you to send emails and other types of messages to us or to third parties and to participate in bulletin boards and discussion groups. All such emails, messages, postings to bulletin boards and discussion groups become our property once you submit them. Whenever you choose to initiate these kinds of communication with us, or anyone else, you may be contacted in return. Also, remember that our bulletin boards and discussion groups are open to the public, and, therefore, your postings can be seen by anyone and are not protected by us or any other entity. Please use your discretion when deciding whether and what to post and whom to contact. We reserve the right, in our sole discretion, to monitor, edit or delete postings from our bulletin boards and discussion groups. This reservation of rights shall not under any circumstances obligate us to conduct such edits or deletions, nor shall it cause us to be liable for any such edits or deletions.

**Use of Your Information**

If you choose to provide us with the above mentioned information, you consent to the use, transfer, processing and storage of the information so provided by you on our servers. The information provided by you shall not be given to third parties (third parties for this purpose do not include our group / holding / subsidiary companies and or our service partners / associates) for marketing purposes and other related activities without your prior consent. Though if you choose to make your profile visible, all information pertaining to your profile will be visible to third parties.

The information provided by you shall be used by us to:

  1. Improve our website and enable us to provide you the most user-friendly experience which is safe, smooth and customized;
  2. Improve and customize our services, content and other commercial / non-commercial features on the website;
  3. Contact you to get your opinion on our current products and services or possible new products and/or services that may be offered by us.
  4. Send you information on our products, services, special deals, promotions;
  5. Ask you to send feedback on any or all of our services;
  6. Send you marketing/promotional communications (If you do not wish to receive such marketing/promotional communications from us you may indicate your preferences at the time of registration or by following the instructions provided on the website or by providing instructions to this effect);
  7. Create various surveys and analysis in form of reports;
  8. Send newsletter(s) to you (Provided you subscribe to the same)
  9. Send you service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so;
  10. Provide you the opportunity to participate in contests or surveys on our website (If you participate, we may request certain additional personally identifiable information from you. Moreover, participation in these surveys or contests is shall be completely voluntary and you therefore shall have a choice whether or not to disclose such additional information);
  11. Contact you or send you e-mail or other communications regarding updates of our Services or additional Services which may be of your interest.
  12. Provide customer support and the services you request; Ascertain how many people visit our website, of what kind and what areas they visit,on our website; 
  13. Resolve disputes, if any and troubleshooting;
  14. Avoid/check illegal and/or potentially prohibited activities and to enforce Agreements
  15. Provide service updates and promotional offers related to our services/products.
  16. Comply with any court judgment / decree / order / directive / legal & government authority /applicable law;
  17. Investigate potential violations or applicable national & international laws;
  18. Investigate deliberate damage to the website/services or its legitimate operation;
  19. Detect, prevent, or otherwise address security and/or technical issues;
  20. Protect the rights, property or safety of FEVL and/or its Directors, employees and the general public at large;
  21. Respond to Claims of third parties;
  22. The members of our corporate family and group, affiliates, service providers and third parties under a contract to provide joint services, contents and marketing communications;
  23. Other third parties to whom you explicitly require us to send the information;

If you consent to receive information about third party opportunities, products or services or you make your profile visible we may disclose your information to such third parties for sending you communications via e-mail or otherwise to inform about services/products which may be of your interest. Also we might use your personal information to communicate with you and ascertain if you are interested in third party services.

Your information shall be disclosed to our service providers who provide services to us vis-a-vis our website and the services/products therein. These service providers/employees will have access to the information provided by you in order to perform their functions/services efficiently.

Based upon the personally identifiable information you provide us, we will send you a welcoming email to verify your username and password. We will also communicate with you in response to your inquiries with respect to our services/content, to provide the services you request, and to manage your account. We will communicate with you by email or telephone, in accordance with your wishes. We will also send you SMS alerts from time to time to update you on relevant information and other updates.

In order to provide certain services to you, we may on occasion supplement the personal information you submitted to us with information from third party sources (third parties for this purpose may include our group / holding / subsidiary companies and or our service partners /associates). We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our website.

**Tailored Advertising**

The Services may include third party tailored ad technology which enables customized ads to be displayed to you through the Services. We do not share personal information with these third parties; however, when you use the Services, we or third parties operating the ad serving technology may use non-personal information that is collected through cookies, anonymous identifiers to ensure that appropriate ads are presented and to perform analytics concerning your use of the Services and other websites tracked by these third parties. These technologies also may control the number of times you see a given ad, deliver ads that relate to your interests, and measure the effectiveness of ad campaigns. To the extent any of this information is collected by third parties, you acknowledge and agree that such collection and use is governed by those third parties’ privacy policies and we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such third parties.

If you are interested in more information about tailored ads and your choices to prevent third parties from delivering tailored ads, you may visit the such third party websites and show your constraints and opt out of such usage of information. Please note that to the extent ad technology is integrated into the Services, you may still receive ads even if you opt-out of tailored ads. In that case, the ads will just not be tailored to your interests.

**Disclosure of Your Information**

We may share your information in the following ways:

  * We may make information collected through the Services available to subsidiaries and affiliated companies that are under common ownership or control within our group companies.
  * We may share information about our visitors, customers, or former customers with the following types of companies that perform services on our behalf or with whom we have joint marketing agreements: 
  * Non-financial companies such as envelope stuffers, fulfillment service providers, payment processors, data processors, customer/support services, etc.
  * Financial service providers such as companies engaged in banking, mortgage lending, consumer finance, securities, and insurance.
  * We may share or sell information about you with other companies who we believe may have products and services of interest to you. If you would like to opt-out of our sharing of your information with these other companies, please follow the “Opting Out of Emails” instructions below.
  * We may share your information with any person or entity where we believe in good faith that such disclosure is necessary to: (a) comply with the law or in response to a subpoena, court order, government request, or other legal process; (b) produce relevant documents or information in connection with litigation, arbitration, mediation, adjudication, government or internal investigations, or other legal or administrative proceedings; (c) protect the interests, rights, safety, or property of the Company or others; (d) enforce the Terms of Use on the Services; (e) provide users of the Services with the services they request; (f) provide you with special offers or promotions from us; (g) allow another company that acquires the Company or some or all of its assets to continue to serve you; or (h) operate the Company's systems properly.
  * We may share your information with any person or entity when we have your consent.
  * We may use and share non-personal information about you or use of the services, including any de-identified and aggregated data with third parties without limitation.

**Opting Out of Emails**

To receive email newsletters and other promotional email communications, users must voluntarily sign up on the website either by creating a profile or by choosing newsletter preferences. From time to time we may send you email notices or news updates alerting you to new features, products, promotions, or services pertaining to our website offerings. If you no longer wish to receive promotional materials from us, you may opt out of receiving these communications by choosing an “Unsubscribe” option available as a link in every email or by contacting us at htcampus@hindustantimes.com. We will gladly comply with all requests for removal. Certain transactional emails such as confirmations of bidder registration are not included in emails that one can opt out of. Transactional emails can be recognized by a lack of an “Unsubscribe” link in the email body.

If you do not want us to share your personal information with third parties for their own marketing purposes, please contact us at htcampus@hindustantimes.com. 

Please note that these opt-out processes may take some time to complete, consistent with applicable law.

**Security and Account Protection**

We have implemented commercially reasonable physical, administrative, technical, and electronic security measures to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of your personal information. Despite our best efforts, however, no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. We appreciate your help in safeguarding the integrity of your own and others’ privacy. We encourage you to let us know immediately if you suspect that any personal information you shared with us is being used contrary to this Privacy Statement.

**Internal Service Providers**

We may use third parties that we refer to as internal service providers to facilitate or outsource one or more aspects of the business, product and service operations that we provide to you on the Site (e.g., search technology, discussion boards, bill collection, affiliate and rewards programs, co-branded credit cards) and therefore we may provide some of your personal information directly to these internal service providers. These internal service providers' are subject to confidentiality agreements with us and other legal restrictions that prohibit their use of the information we provide them for any other purpose except to facilitate the specific outsourced Site related operation, unless you have explicitly agreed or given your prior permission to them for additional uses. In some instances, the internal service provider may collect information directly from you (such as for Site surveys or for a co-branded credit card). In these cases, you will be notified of the involvement of the internal service provider, and all additional information you provide them and their additional uses will be strictly up to you. If you provide additional information to an internal service provider directly, then their use of your personal information is governed by their applicable privacy policy. FEVL is not responsible or liable for the privacy practices or content of third parties.

**Other Corporate Entities**

We share much of our data, including personal information about you, with our parent, affiliates, subsidiaries, and joint ventures that are committed to serving your online trading needs and related services, throughout the world. To the extent that these entities have access to your information, they will treat it at least as protectively as they treat information they obtain from their other users. Our parent, affiliates, subsidiaries, and joint ventures follow privacy practices no less protective of all users than our practices described in this document, to the extent allowed by applicable law. FEVL, its parent, affiliates, subsidiaries, its joint ventures, or any combination of such, will share some or all of your personal information with another business entity should we plan to, merge with, or be acquired by that business entity. Should such a combination occur, we will require that the new combined entity follow this privacy policy with respect to your personal information. 

**Accessing, Reviewing, And Changing Personal Information**

We will take reasonable steps to ensure that the information and data on the Services is complete and accurate. If your personal information changes, is inaccurate, or if you no longer wish to use the Services, contact us at htcampus@hindustantimes.com to correct or update the information.

**Legal Requests**

We cooperate with law enforcement and regulatory inquiries, as well as other third parties to enforce laws, such as: intellectual property rights, fraud and other rights, to help protect you and the community from bad actors. Therefore, in response to a verified request by law enforcement or other government officials relating to a criminal investigation or alleged illegal activity, we can (and you authorize us to) disclose your name, city, state, telephone number, email address, UserID history, fraud complaints, and bidding and listing history without a subpoena. Without limiting the above, in an effort to respect your privacy and our ability to keep the community free from bad actors, we will not otherwise disclose your personal information to law enforcement or other government officials without a subpoena, court order or substantially similar legal procedure, except when we believe in good faith that the disclosure of information is necessary to prevent imminent physical harm or financial loss; or report suspected illegal activity. Further, we can (and you authorize us to) disclose your name, street address, city, state, PIN code, country, phone number, email, and company name to Intellectual Property right's owners under confidentiality agreement, as we in our sole discretion believe necessary or appropriate in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringement, piracy, or other unlawful activity. 

Due to the existing regulatory environment, we cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personal information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. By way of example (without limiting the foregoing), we may be forced to disclose personal information to the government or third parties under certain circumstances, third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications, or users may abuse or misuse your personal information that they collect from the Site. Therefore, although we use industry standard practices to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information or private communications will always remain private.

**Third Party Links and Services**

The Services may contain links to third-party websites, including social networking websites. Your use of these features may result in the collection or sharing of information about you, depending on the feature. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of other websites or services to which we link. We do not endorse or make any representations about third-party websites or services. The personal information you choose to provide to or that is collected by these third parties is not covered by our Privacy Statement. We strongly encourage you to read such third parties’ privacy statements.

**Amendments to Privacy Statement**

We may amend this Privacy Statement at any time by posting the amended terms on the Services. Any changes to this Statement will become effective upon posting. Your continued use of the Services following these changes means that you accept such revisions. If we make any material changes to this Privacy Statement, we will post the changes here and notify you either via email or by notice on the Services.

**Minor's Privacy**

Minor are not eligible to use our Site and we ask that minors (under the age of 18) do not submit any personal information to us. If you are under the age of 18, you cannot sell, purchase or bid for any items on the Site. If you wish to purchase or sell an item on the Site such purchase or sale may be made by your legal guardian or parents who have registered as users of the Site provided that such purchase or sale is not in relation to any adult material/mature audience items displayed on the Site, the sale or purchase of which to/by minors is strictly prohibited.

**International Transfers of Information**

Some of the uses and disclosures mentioned in this Privacy Statement may involve the transfer of your personal information to various countries around the world that may have different levels of privacy protection than your country. By submitting your personal information, you consent to such transfers. 

**Cookies**

We use cookies on the website but do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our website. We do not set cookies to store your passwords. If you reject cookies, you will still use our website. We have no access to or control over third party cookies and we don't store any cookies and just use the facility of .net framework for page output cache. This privacy statement does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**Changing Your Personal Information**

You can access and modify your personal information by signing on to the website. We will not modify the information provided by you. However, you must update your personal information as soon as such changes are necessitated. 

Where you make a public posting, you may not be able to change or remove it nor shall you be able to close your account. Upon your request, we will close your account and remove your personal information from view as soon as reasonably possible, based on your account activity and in accordance with applicable law(s). However, we will retain your personal information from closed accounts to comply with law, Avoid/check illegal and/or potentially prohibited activities and to enforce User Agreements; Comply with any court judgment / decree / order / directive / legal & government authority /applicable law; Investigate potential violations or applicable national & international laws; Investigate deliberate damage to the website/services or its legitimate operation; Detect, prevent, or otherwise address security and/or technical issues; Protect the rights, property or safety of FEVL and/or its Directors, employees and the general public at large; Respond to Claims of third parties; and take such other actions as may be permitted by law.

**Account Protection**

Your password is the key to your account. You shall be solely responsible for all the activities happening under your username and you shall be solely responsible for keeping your password secure. Do not disclose your password to anyone. If you share your password or your personal information with others, you shall be solely responsible for all actions taken under your username and you may lose substantial control over your personal information and may be subject to legally binding actions taken on your behalf. Therefore, if your password has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately change your password.

**Business Transaction**

In the event FEVL goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personally identifiable information will likely be among the assets transferred.

**Security**

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter your personal information we treat the data as an asset that must be protected and use tools (encryption, passwords, physical security, etc.) to protect your personal information against unauthorized access and disclosure. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security nor can we guarantee that third parties shall not unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications, and that other users may abuse or misuse your personal information that you provide. Therefore, although we work hard to protect your information, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information or private communications will always remain private.

**Links to Other Sites**

The website contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by FEVL. Please be aware that we, FEVL and/or the website, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies only to information collected by the website or to our other related websites provided it appears at the footer of the page therein. It does not apply to third party advertisements which appear on our websites and we suggest you read the privacy statements of such advertisers.

**Changes in this Privacy Statement**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement and such other places we deem appropriate so that you are updated about the manner we collect information, what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently at our website.

**Contacting Us**

Should you have any questions about this Privacy Statement, contact us by sending an email to htcampus@hindustantimes.com. Please provide your name, mailing address, telephone number and email address so we can service you more quickly. You can also call us at 0124-3954731.

We may record the conversations our agents or employees have with you. We do this from time to time to monitor the quality of service and accuracy of information our agents and employees give to you and to ensure that your instructions are followed. No agent or employee of the Company is authorized to waive any provisions of our Company policies and procedures.
